Now that base is on, we're going to move on to the lid color.
For the lid color, you have so many choices.
Like I said, I'm going to go with something that goes along with the theme of clothes she's wearing.
Kind of like in the plums, eggplants.
I'm going to use kind of a plum brown that has a shimmer to it.
There's so many you could use.
You could use one that's more lavender, more bronze.
There's just an assortment of colors you can choose.
I like this one because it's got a bit of an iridescence to it.
It goes on really smooth and it's just dark enough to be a lid color, but not dark enough to be a crease color.
I'm going to take a smaller brush and I'm going to go right into this color.
You want to put a little at a time until it gets to your desired depth of color.
You're going to put it directly on the lid.
The lid is basically from where the eyelash is.
Meet the lid to up to the crease.
This is basically your lid where the ball of the eye protrudes.
You don't want to go any higher than this because you want to keep this highlighted under the brow, but you want to get as close to the lashes as you can.
You want everything to just look blended and balanced.
It's all about blending, blending, blending.
Add a little more and a little more if you want it to be darker and darker.
If you spill a little bit, that's fine.
Just clean it up with a brush afterwards.
It's not a big deal.
Open.
I'm going to do it a little darker since it's an evening look.
You can get dramatic and just blend, blend, blend.
There we go.
It's a beautiful lid color.